(gentle music)
♪ Uh, uh, uh ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I was thinking 'bout her,
thinking 'bout me ♪
♪ Thinking 'bout us ♪
♪ What we gon' be ♪
♪ Opened my eyes, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ So I traveled back
down that road ♪
♪ Will she come back,
no one knows ♪
♪ I realize, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ I was at the top and now
it's like I'm in the basement ♪
♪ Number one spot and now
she found her a replacement ♪
♪ I swear now I can't take it ♪
♪ Knowing somebody's
got my baby ♪
♪ And now you ain't around
baby I can't think ♪
♪ I should've put it down,
should've got the ring ♪
♪ 'Cause I can still
feel it in the air ♪
♪ See her pretty face,run my
fingers through her hair ♪
♪ My love of my life,
my shawty, my wife ♪
♪ She left me, I'm tight ♪
♪ 'Cause I knew that
it just ain't right ♪
♪ I was thinking 'bout her,
thinking 'bout me ♪
♪ Thinking 'bout us,
what we gon' be ♪
♪ Opened my eyes, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ So I traveled back
down that road ♪
♪ Will she come back,
no one knows ♪
♪ I realize, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ When I be ridin', man ♪
♪ I swear I see her
face at every turn ♪
♪ Tryna get my Usher on
but I can't let it burn ♪
♪ And I just hope she know that
she the only one I yearn for ♪
♪ More and more I miss
her, when will I learn ♪
♪ Didn't give her all my love,
I guess now I got my payback ♪
♪ Now I'm in the club
thinking all about my baby ♪
♪ Hey, she was so easy to love ♪
♪ But wait, I guess that
love wasn't enough ♪
♪ I'm going through it
every time that I'm alone ♪
♪ And now I'm missing, wishing
she'd pick up the phone ♪
♪ But she made the decision
that she wanted to move on ♪
♪ 'Cause I was wrong ♪
♪ I was thinking 'bout her,
thinking 'bout me ♪
♪ Thinking 'bout us,
what we gon' be ♪
♪ Opened my eyes, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ So I traveled back
down that road ♪
♪ Will she come back,
no one knows ♪
♪ I realize, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ If you ever loved
somebody put your hands up ♪
♪ And now they're gone
and you're wishing ♪
♪ You could give
them everything ♪
♪ Said if you ever loved
somebody put your hands up ♪
♪ If you ever loved somebody
put your hands up ♪
♪ Now they're gone
and you're wishing ♪
♪ You could give
them everything ♪
♪ I was thinking 'bout her,
thinking 'bout me ♪
♪ Thinking 'bout us,
what we gon' be ♪
♪ Opened my eyes, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ So I traveled back
down that road ♪
♪ Will she come back,
no one knows ♪
♪ I realize, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ I was thinking 'bout her,
thinking 'bout me ♪
♪ Thinking 'bout us,
what we gon' be ♪
♪ Opened my eyes, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪ So I traveled back
down that road ♪
♪ Will she come back,
no one knows ♪
♪ I realize, yeah,
it was only just a dream ♪
♪♪♪